Guide to the Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015.]
Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015]
- Series II: Audiotapes
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Post -Traumatic Stress Disorder" by JoAnn Difede; "Bad Food Labeling Laws" by Alan Mathios; "School-Age Childcare Programs" by Polly Spedding; "Whales '93" by Christopher Clark; "Urban Sprawl and Farmland" by Tom Hirschl - Cornell Film, Week of August 23, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Unintegrated Emotion and Hypertension" by Samuel Mann; "Frugal Spending" by Amy Dacyczyn; "Workplace of the Future" by Morton Bahr; "Pre-Occluded Virus" by Alan Wood; "Pesticide Risks in Growing Produce" by Bob Seem - Cornell Film, Week of August 30, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Potential new Asthma Treatment" by Kendall Smith; "Hidden Inflation" by Jeanne Hogarth; "Sexual Assault on College Campuses" by Andrea Parrot; "Concept Mapping" by Joseph Novak; "Radon in Rental Property" by Joe Laquatra - Cornell Film, Week of September 6, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Sleep-Deprived Students" by James Maas; "Supermarket Research" by Rosemary Avery; "Math Anxiety" by Shelia Tobias; "CORSIM Model Can Evaluate Health Care Reform" by Steven Caldwell; "Fall Tree and Shrub Planting" by Don Rakow - Cornell Film, Week of September 13, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Noise Induced Hearing Loss on Farms" by Mark Kramer; "Roof Repairs" by Elliot Schrank; "Women in the Military" by Carolyn Becraft; "Nitric oxide Protects the Heart" by Robert Levi; "El Nino and Wild Weather" by Mark Wysocki - Cornell Film, Week of September 20, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Protein and Young Athletes" by Wanda Koszewski; "How to Fix the Airline Industry" by Alfred Kahn; "Football Uniforms Represent the Ideal Male Body Image" by Charlotte Jirousek; "Heat- Resistant Molds by Don Splittstoesser; "Leaf Composting by Tom Richard - Cornell Film, Week of September 27, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Mental Stress Tests" by Thomas Pickering; "Food Handling Labels" by Donna Scott; "Home Fire Escape Plan" by Joe DeMarco; "Woodchucks and Hepatitis B" by Bud Tennant; "Bovine Somatotropin/Environmentally Cleaner Cows" by Dale Bauman - Cornell Film, Week of October 4, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Male Infertility" by Marc Goldstein; "Early Retirement" by Olivia Mitchell; "Study habits for College Freshman" by Helene Selco; "Improving Comfort and Safety in Surgical Gowns" by Susan Ashdown; "Birdseed Preference Study" by Margaret Barker - Cornell Film, Week of October 11, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Increased Weight Gain During Pregnancy" by Christine Olson; "Home Environmental Audits" by Joe Laquatra; "Homelessness and the Clinton Budget" by Fred Karnas; "Improvements in Echocardiography" by Richard Devereux; "Waste Prevention Through Brown Bag Lunches" by Ellen Harrison - Cornell Film, Week of October 18, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "H. Pylori and Ulcers" by Paul Miskovitz; "Automobile Repair Fraud" by Lois Morton; "Maltreated Kids and Poor Academic Performance" by John Eckenrode; "Robotic Grape Pruner" by Wesley Gunkel; "Avoiding Deer-Car Collisions" by Paul Curtis - Cornell Film, Week of October 25, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Seasonal Affective Disorder" by Margaret Moline; "Pinning Job Hopes on Small Businesses" by Ruth Young; "Decorative Corn" by Marcia Eames-Sheavly; "Science for Non-Scientist" by Bruce Ganem; "Whale Census Through Navy's IUSS System" by Christopher Clark - Cornell Film, Week of November 1, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Cystic Fibrosis" by Mary DiMaio; "Home Shopping Television Networks" by Rosemary Avery; "Positive Affect" by Alice Isen; "Bioremediation of Pollutants" by Eugene Madsen; "Snow Atlas" by Warren Knapp and Dan Wilks - Cornell Film, Week of November 8, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Demo Tape" - Cornell Film, November 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Kicking the Smoking Habit" by Gilbert Botvin; "Thanksgiving Food Safety" by Donna Scott; "Low SAT Scores and Textbooks" by Donald Hayes; "Hubble Telescope Repair" by Yervant Terzian; "Effect of Air Pollution on our Psyche" by Gary Evans - Cornell Film, Week of November 15, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Depo-Provera" by Margaret Polaneczky; "Impact of job Turnover on Workers" by John Bishop; "Decline of Hunting " by Jody Enck; "Math and Science for the Blind" by John Gardner; "Decrease in Acid Precipitation" by Mark Wysocki - Cornell Film, Week of November 22, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Multiple Sclerosis" by Brian Apatoff; "Holiday Spending/Budgeting" by Lois Morton; "Single Parent Poverty" by Thomas Hirschl; "Faster Transistors" by Yosef Shacham and Kaushik Bhaumik; "Holiday Waste Reduction" by Clare Hinrichs - Cornell Film, Week of November 29, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Winter Skin Care" by Rachelle Scott; "Sports Helmets as Holiday Gifts" by Lois Chaplin; "Holiday Fire safety" by Joe DeMarco; "Nitric Oxide and Viral Infections" by John MacMicking; "Deep Sea Exploration" by Charles Greene - Cornell Film, Week of December 6, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Holiday Overeating" by Martha McKittrick; "Discount Club Stores" by Rosemary Avery; "Holliday Pet Safety" by Larry Thompson; "Stone-Washed Denim" by Charlotte Coffman; "Back to the Biosphere" by Robert Howarth - Cornell Film, Week of December 13, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Holiday Depression" by John Markowitz; "Holiday Gift Return Policies" by Josephine Swanson; "Personality and Obesity" by Virginia Utermohlen and Terry Horner; "Dinosaurs and Birds" by John Chiment; "Holiday Waste Disposal" by Ken Cobb - Cornell Film, Week of December 20, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Winter Back Pain" by Frank Morosky; "1994 Economic Outlook" by Alfred Kahn; "Housing for the Homeless" by Julie Sandorf; "Ultra sonic Aeroponics" by Laura Matthews; "Christmas Tree Disposal" by David Taber - Cornell Film, Week of December 27, 1993 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Proscar to Prevent Prostate Cancer" by Richard Silver; "Winter Preparedness Around the Home" by Lois Morton; "Sick Building Syndrome and Smoking policies" by Alan Hedge; "Lasers in Ophthalmology" by Philip Lempert; "Global Ecology" by Harold Mooney - Cornell Film, Week of January 3, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Blood Use" by Carl Wolf; "Do you Need a tax Preparer?" by Jeanne Hogarth; "Illiteracy in the Workforce" by Vernon Briggs; "Spinal Cord Injuries" by Alex Simotas; "Suburban Deer Management" by Paul Curtis - Cornell Film, Week of January 10, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Sleep apnea" by Margaret Moline; "Frugal Spending on Groceries" by Amy Dacyczyn; "President Clinton's Fist Year" by Theodore Lowi; "Controlled Environment Agriculture" by Robert Langhans; "School Waste Prevention" by Ellen Harrison - Cornell Film, Week of January 17, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Varicocele and Male Infertility" by Marc Goldstein; "Home Inventory" by Jeanne Hogarth; "Winter tips For the Elderly" by Naomi Miner; "Athletic Apparel for the Olympics" by Nancy Breen; "Nuclear Waste Storage" by Duane Chapman and Jon Erickson - Cornell Film, Week of February 7,1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Depression and Heart Attack" by Robert Allan; "The Wine Navigator" by Doug Hexter; "How to Stay Warm" by Peter Schwartz; "Supercomputers and the Atmosphere" by Kate Kirby; "Alternative Household Cleansers" by Ann Lemley - Cornell Film, Week of February 14, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Marfan's Syndrome" by Richard Devereux; "Grocery Shopping with Credit Cards" by Lois Morton; "Parental control of Television" by Florence Cherry; "New Technologies to Treat Enlarged Prostate" by Aaron Perlmutter; "Planning New Tree Plantings" by David Taber - Cornell Film, Week of February 21, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Smoking During Pregnancy can Lower Child's IQ" by Charles Henderson; "Speed Advisories" by Lynne Irwin; "Children and Funerals" by Suzanne West; "Solar powered Appliances" by Joe Laquatra; "Importance of Wetlands" by Barbara Bedford - Cornell Film, Week of February 28, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Calcium's effect on Iron Absorption" by Dennis Miller; "Opening a Restaurant" by Christopher Muller; "Suicide and "Final Exit"" by Peter Marzuk; "Biotechnology and Dentistry" by Gordon Douglas; "Weather Forecasting Tools and Accuracy" by Mark Wysocki - Cornell Film, Week of March 7, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Disease-Mongering" by Lynn Payer; "Teaching Kids Money Management" by Josephine Swanson; "Self Defense Devices" by George Sutfin; "Excimer Laser Surgery for Myopia" by Philip Lempert; "Gap Analysis" by Charles Smith - Cornell Film, Week of March 14, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Reducing Anxiety" by Alan Manevitz; "Potholes" by Lynne Irwin; "Why people Volunteer" by Don Tobais; "High Resolution Disease Forecasting" by Robert Seem; "Unsafe Municipal Compost" by Don Lisk - Cornell Film, Week of April 4, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Breast Self Examination" by Bonnie Reichman; "Radon and New Homes" by Joe Laquatra; "Public Hearings" by Lois Morton; "Science Education-What's Wrong with it " by Shelia Tobias; "Acid Snow" by Mark Wysocki - Cornell Film, Week of April 11, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Kids and Poisons" by Ann Dimaio; "Employer Support of Child Care" by Jeanne Hogarth; "How Child Care Benefits the Family" by Urie Bronfenbrenner; "Detecting Eye Problems in Infants" by Joelle Mast; "Teaching Young Kids About the Environment" by Jean Bonhotal - Cornell Film, Week of April 18,1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Starting an Exercise Program" by Elisabeth Lachmann; "Cooperatives" by Brian Henehan; "Strong Families, Strong Soldiers" by Marney Thomas; "Improved Pesticide Application Technology" by Richard Derksen; "International Migratory Bird Day" by Martha Fischer - Cornell Film, Week of Apr. 25, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Ear protection" by Samuel Selesnick; "Hob Prospects for College Grads" by John Bishop; "Test Anxiety" by Helene Seco; "Gene Therapy for Cystic Fibrosis" by Noel McIlvaney; "Lawn Preparation" by Norm Hummel - Cornell Film, Week of May 2, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Insomnia" by Margaret Moline; "Writing a Will" by Jeanne Hogarth; "Smoke Detectors" by Joe DeMarco; "Map-Based Cloning" by Elizabeth Earle; "Getting Soil Ready for Planting" by Tom Weiler - Cornell Film, Week of May 9, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Phytomedicine" by Steven Foster; "Fraud Against the Elderly" by Lois Morton; "Impact of Zoning Laws on the Elderly" by Patricia Baron Pollak; "Nitric Oxide and Stroke" by John Wagner; "Protecting Tress Against Gypsy Moths" by Carolyn Klass - Cornell Film, Week of May 16, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Living Wills/Health Care Proxy" by Richard Beresford; "Pay Equity" by Susan Bianchi-Sand; "The Allure of Smoking" by Richard Klein; "Preventing Further Damage in Spinal Injuries" by Frank Cammisa; "Regional Climate Centers" by Warren Knapp - Cornell Film, Week of May 23, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Summer Weight Loss and Cookouts" by Matha McKittrick; "Moisture Damage in the Attic" by Elliot Schrank; "Bicycle Helmet Laws" by Lois Chaplin; "Pesticide Resistance Among Flies" by David Soderlund; "The Asian Lady Beetle" by Richard Hoebeke - Cornell Film, Week of May 30, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Sunglasses" by Calvin Roberts; "Choosing Carpet" by Peter Schwartz; "Youth and Senior Volunteering Together" by Karl Pillemer; "Constructed Wetlands for Leachate Treatment" by John Peverly; "Saving Seabirds" by Stephen Kress - Cornell Film, Week of June 6, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Children and Sun Exposure" by Rachelle Scott; "Summer Gas Prices" by Duane Chapman; "Coping with Sexual Loss as a Result of Medical Conditions" by Constance Shapiro; "ATOC System for Measuring Global Warming" by Christopher Clark; "Debate Over Deforestation" by Gordon Orians - Cornell Film, Week of June 13, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Exercise and Air Pollution" by Abe Sanders; "Summer Driving Checkup" by Lynne Irwin; "Sexual Harassment in Blue Collar Jobs" by Francine Moccio; "4-D G-I-S" by Charles Greene; "ATOC and Whales" by Katy Payne - Cornell Film, Week of June 20, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 10)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Vaccines and Kids" by Paul Edelson; "Stinging insects" by Roger Morse; "School Choice" by Michael Joseph; "Laparascopy" by Philip Barie; "Sewage Sludge" by Jack Martin - Cornell Film, Week of August 12,1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Medical Testing" by Louis Aronne; "Retirement Planning" by Amanda Sherwin; "Preparing Kids or School" by Ladd Speigel; "Resveratrol" by Lee Creasy; "Economics of Recycling" by Daryl Ditz - Cornell Film, Week of August 19, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Glaucoma" by Gregory Harmon; "Back -To-School Clothing" by Charlotte Coffman; "Labor Unions" by Jack Sheinkman; "Monitoring Pollutants" by Terrill Cool; "Garbage Tags" by Ellen Harrison; - Cornell Film, Week of August 26, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Fall Allergies/Dust Mites" by Gillian Shepherd; "Lead Paint" by Joe Laquatra; ""SCANS" Study" by John Wirt; "Surgical Sutures" by C.C.Chu; "Fall Lawn Fertilizing" by Marty Petrovik - Cornell Film, Week of September 2, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "High Blood Pressure" by Samuel Mann; "Advertising in Schools" by Josephine Swanson; "Developing Good Study Habits" by Helene Selco; "Landfill Liners" by Tom O'Rourke and Anil Netravali; "Preserving The Environment" by Andrew Zepp - Cornell Film, Week of September 9, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Doctors and Technology" by Stephen Scheidt; "Fall House hunting" by Peter Zorn; "Farm Safety Week " by John Pollock; "Intelligent Houses" by Jim McCarty; "Environmental Policies" by Richard Booth - Cornell Film, Week of September 16, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Swallowing Disorders" by Arnon Lambroza; "Self-Employment" by Robert Aronson; "Air Bags" by Lynne Irwin; "Rebirth of Nuclear Power" by Bingham Cady; "Puffins" by Stephen Kress - Cornell Film, Week of September 23,1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Calcium After Menopause" by Richard Rivlin; "Energy-Efficient Homes" by Joe Laquatra; "Personnel Testing" by Leatta Hough; "Fertility Treatment for Neurologically Impaired Males" by J. Francois Eid; "Car/Deer Collisions" by Paul Curtis - Cornell Film, Week of September 30, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Neurobehavior Evaluation Program" by David Silbersweig; "Women's Wages Lower than Men's" by Jennifer Gerner; "Redeveloping Rural America" by Jerome Zigler; "Bow-Head Whales" by Chris Clark; "Doubts about Bioremediation" by Robert Howarth - Cornell Film, Week of October 7, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Dental Care " by David Behrman; "Target Marketing" by Enrique Figueroa; "Brown Bag School Lunch Safety" by Donna Scott; "Interferon and Bone Marrow Disorders" by Richard Silver; "Leaf Composting" by Tom Richard - Cornell Film, Week of October 14, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Flu Shots" by Marc Weksler; "Home Foreclosure" by Jeanne Hogarth; "Feeding the Homeless" by Robert Egger; "Taste Changes" by Bruce Halpern; "Social/ Economic Concerns of Pesticide use" by David Pimentel - Cornell Film, Week of October 21, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Selenium and Colon Cancer" by Gerald Combs; "Bank Mergers" by Uri Possen; "Women in Politics" by Isaac Kramnick; "Transplant Rejection" by Jon Clardy; "Bird Feeders" by Gregory Butcher - Cornell Film, Week of October 28, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Coping With Alzheimer's Disease" by Gerald Addonizio; "Catalog Shopping" by Josephine Swanson; "Winterizing Your Home" by Jim McCarty; "Computer Simulation of Cardiac Blood Flow" by Charles Peskin; "Preventing Deer Damage" by Paul Curtis - Cornell Film, Week of November 4, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Diabetes" by Robert Campbell; Microwave Vegetables" by Gertrude Armbruster; "Housing Problems for Women" by Joe Laquatra; "Thermal Fabrics" by Muthu Govindaraj; "Prospecting for Chemicals" by Tom Eisner - Cornell Film, Week of November 11, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Smoking Cessation- Great American Smokeout Tie-in" by Gilbert Botvin; "Cost and Health Benefits of Turkey" by Paul Aho; "National/Standardized Testing" by Michael Joseph; "A-L-S in Horses" by John Cummings; "Global Warming Negotiations" by William Nitze - Cornell Film, Week of November 18, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Holiday Overeating" by Jodie Goodman and Erica Leon; "Holiday Spending" by Jeanne Hogarth; "Troubled Teens" by Harriette McAdoo; "Smart Materials" by Rishi Raj; "Abiogenic Gas and Oil" by Thomas Gold - Cornell Film, Week of November 25, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Toxoplasmosis" by William Ledger; "Holiday Travel Tips" by Mac Noden; "Selecting a Christmas Tree" by David Taber; "Bucky Balls" by Arthur Ruoff; "Making Biological Control Work" by Robert Granados - Cornell Film, Week of December 2, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Hypothermia" by Alexander Kuehl; "Kid's Buying Power" by Josephine Swanson; "Winter Driving Precautions" by Toni Rosenbaum; "Gene Mapping in Plants" by Steven Tanksley; "Environmental Applications of Remote Sensing" by William Philpot - Cornell Film, Week of December 9, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Holiday Depression" by Ron Mack; "End of Year Tax Savings" by Dale Grossman; "Meaning of Christmas" by Sue West; "Technology for the Disabled" by Richard Read; "Calcium Magnesium Acetate" by Lynne Irwin - Cornell Film, Week of December 16, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Winter Fitness" by Willibald Nagler; "Food Safety Knowledge" by Bob Gravani; "Christmas Memories" by Diane Ackerman; "Winter Sky" by Terry Herter; "Christmas Tree Dispoisal" by David Taber - Cornell Film, Week of December 23, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Flu Treatments" by Marc Weksler; "1992 Economic Outlook" by Alfred Kahn; "New- Years Resolutions" by Ladd Spiegel; "Artificial Intelligence" by Harry Collins; "Climate Change as National Security" by Fen Hampson - Cornell Film, Week of December 30, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Sunscreens in Winter" by Sheryl Clark; "Lack of Energy Efficiency" by Joe Laquatra; "Healthcare for the Homeless" by Bob Prentice; "New Uses For M- R- I" by Lynn Jelinski; "Environmental Shopping" by Jeanne Hogarth - Cornell Film, Week of January 6, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "AIDS and Athletes" by David Rogers; "Post- Holiday Credit Card Bills" by Bob Avery; "Handicapped Accessibility" by Charles Goldman; "Human Genomes" by Stephe O' Brien; "Labor and The Environment" by John Funiciello - Cornell Film, Week of January 13, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Beta Carotoene and UV light" by Daphne Roe; "Food Labeling" by Christina Stark; "Super Bowl Mania" by Tom Gilovich; "New Way to Measure Blood Pressure" by Seymour Blank; "Carbon Dioxide and Photosynthesis" by William Ogren - Cornell Film, Week of January 20, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "M-D- R Tuberculosis" by Joseph Cook; "Item Pricing" by Dick Wittink; "Malnourished Kids" by Reynaldo Martorell; "Optical Disc Storage" by Watt Webb; "Amateur Weather Forecasting" by Marc Wysocki - Cornell Film, Week of January 27, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Women and Heart Disease" by Ellen Mellow; "Carpeting as Health Hazard" by Clark Garner; "Unions in the Nineties" by Bruce Raynor; "IRIS" by Peter Loucks; "Conservation Funds" by Stephen Kress - Cornell Film, Week of February 3, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Physical Exams" by Charles Bardes; "Home Refinancing" by Jeanne Hogarth; "Valentine's Day" by Diane Ackerman; "UV Light and Plants" by Rob Last; "Environmental Philosophy" by Dale Jamieson - Cornell Film, Week of February 10, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Winter Itch" by Sheryl Clark; "Impact of Airline Deregulation" by Alfred Kahn; "Child Abuse" by Phillip Hayden; "Gene Mapping and Plant Diversity" by Steven Tanksley; "Mixed Waste Composting" by Tom Richard - Cornell Film, Week of February 17, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Lovastatin and Heart Disease" by Bruce Gordon; "Inheritance" by Bob Avery; "Egyptian Influences on Greek Civilization" by Martin Bernal; "Testing for a New Planetary System" by Stuart Shapiro and Saul Teukolsky; "Elephants/ Ivory Trade Ban - Cornell Film, Week of February 24, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Marfan's Syndrome" by Mary Roman; "Shoulder Season/ Travel" by Mac Noden; "Alcohol use Among Young People" by John Gormley; "Women in Science" by Ann Hibner-Koblitz; "Dolphin-Safe Tuna" by Joe Regenstein - Cornell Film, Week of March 2, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Yo-Yo Dieting" by Mary Abbott Hess; "Supermarkets in the Year 2000" by Edward McLaughlin; "Financing a College Education" by Don Saleh; "Mars Observer Mission" by Steven Squyres; "Zebra Mussels" by Ed Mills - Cornell Film, Week of March 9, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Early Detection of Prostate Cancer" by Peter Schlegel; "Earned Income Tax Credit" by Jeanne Hogarth; "Women's Worth" by Bernice Sandler; "Technology and Correspondence Courses" by Gary Keisling; "Biotechnology's Impact on Agriculture" by Lynn Jelinski - Cornell Film, Week of March 16, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Panic Disorder" by Katherine Shear; "Home Repair Scams" by Joe McCarty; "Productivity" by David Pearce Snyder; "Insect Chemicals" by Tom Eisner; "Ozone Depletion" by Mark Wysocki - Cornell Film, Week of March 23, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Children and Asthma" by David Valacer; "More Potholes this Year" by Lynne Irwin; "Affordable Housing" by Dale Rosenthal; "Images of Engineers" by Bruce Lewenstein; "Used Oil Disposal" by Ann Lemley - Cornell Film, Week of March 30, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Children and Poison" by Ann DiMaio; "Wealthy/ Poor Gap" by Bob Avery; "Apprenticeship" by Stephen Hamilton; "Developing Mathematical Models for AIDS Transmissions" by Herbert Hethcote; "Biofungicides" by Eric Nelson - Cornell Film, Week of April 6, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Gestational Diabetes" by Andrew Drexler; "Microwave Cooking Tips" by Gertrude Armbruster; "Religious Resurgence" by Bob Johnson; "Bio-Pharming" by Lynn Jelinski; "Ecological Gardening" by Marcia Eames- Sheavly - Cornell Film, Week of April 13, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)
  - CLOSER LOOK Series "Low-Fat Foods" by Lauren Skluth; "Vehicle Corrosion" by Lynne Irwin; "Status of Secretaries" by Jennie Farley; "Potential Cancer Inhibitor in Cow's Milk" by Ronald Gorewit; "Tree Inventory" by Nina Bassuk - Cornell Film, Week of April 20, 1992 (Box 21-36-2566 - 11)